{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044244595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044244595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044269454","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044269454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044279192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044279192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044291298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044291298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044292977","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044292977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044301530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044301530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044306864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044306864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044328980","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044328980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044340946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044340946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044355340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044355340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044370712","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044370712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044385119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044385119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044400183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044400182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044407356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044407356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044407430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044407430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044409395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044409395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044426052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044426051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044435791","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044435791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044444513","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044444513"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044460473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044460473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044482730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044482730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044494947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044494946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044501552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044501552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044517006","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044517006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044543439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044543438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044561850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044561850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044590822","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044590822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044596550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044596550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044609253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044609253"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044625604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044625604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044644507","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044644507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_l"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044663335","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044663335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044672714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044672714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044682328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044682328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_o"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044693914","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044693914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044705503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044705503"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044729875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044729875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044744213","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044744213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044755194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044755193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044763078","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044763078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044771041","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044771041"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_v"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044782674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044782674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_w"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044791357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044791356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044800969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044800969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549044811153","data":{"timestamp":" 1549044811152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190201_210239"," gameId":" 90df8cc7-23f5-4803-889b-23e6bed61ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc_all.asc.A..Z.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}